<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: trend trading | Warrior Wealth]]></title>
  <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/categories/trend-trading/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-09-27T09:03:33-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ken Yu]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[VERI - Buy What's Going Up]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/veri-buy-whats-going-up/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-27T08:53:30-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/veri-buy-whats-going-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>$VERI has been a runner over the past few weeks. The question now is, should we short it?</p>

<p>As trend traders, the last thing we want to do to $VERI is to short it. It&rsquo;s nice to paint tops and have our little egos stroked when this thing comes crashing down fast, but trend traders <em>follow</em> the price movement, not predict it.</p>

<p>Here&rsquo;s the chart on the daily:</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170927/veri_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170927/veri_daily.png" alt="VERI Daily - 2017-09-27" /></a></p>

<p>Today, we have a massive red candle engulfing the prior three trading sessions. As far as we&rsquo;re concerned, the overall trend on the daily chart is going up. Ignoring everything else like news, PE ratios, or whatever fundamental analysis, this chart is a screaming long. As Paul Tudor Jones once said:</p>

<blockquote><p>&ldquo;&hellip;at the end of the day, your job is to buy what goes up and to sell what goes down so really who gives a damn about PE’s? If it’s going up you’re supposed to be long it.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>

<p>Put another way, your goal is to jump in on the trend, up or down, depending on your timeframe. How much risk you&rsquo;re willing to put on this trend trade depends on where you place your stop. Conservative trend traders would place a stop below the existing 50MA, and more aggressive trend traders would place it at a closer MA (20MA).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
