<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: trend | Warrior Wealth]]></title>
  <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/categories/trend/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-09-27T15:10:02-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ken Yu]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[VCEL - Trending Up]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/vcel-trending-up/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-27T15:06:01-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/vcel-trending-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey traders,</p>

<p>One hot stock today is $VCEL. Let&rsquo;s take a look at the chart.</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170927/vcel_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170927/vcel_daily.png" alt="VCEL Daily - 2017-09-27" /></a></p>

<p>$VCEL has breached the 200MA early in July, and held all other moving averages (20, 50, and 100) since then. The momentum continues to the upside, and the trend is strongly upwards. This is, without a doubt, a buy, with a stop loss placed just below the 20MA. While we aren&rsquo;t long this stock, we do have a bullish bias here. As always, should you get long, size your position according to your personal risk tolerance.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[LITE - 200MA Bounce]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/lite-200ma-bounce/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-27T10:41:52-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/lite-200ma-bounce</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey traders,</p>

<p>As small caps continue to grind higher, we can look towards individual stocks to get long. One stock in the small caps in particular is $LITE. Please observe the chart below.</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170927/lite_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170927/lite_daily.png" alt="LITE Daily - 2017-09-27" /></a></p>

<p>$LITE tagged the 200MA yesterday and bounced nicely off of it today. We&rsquo;re looking to jump in on the trend here at a good trade location, with a stop just below the 200MA, at 45.87. According to your personal risk tolerance, size your position accordingly.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eyes on JD]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/eyes-on-jd/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-27T09:23:46-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/eyes-on-jd</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>$JD has shown some decent strength over the past year. More recently, it has pulled back below the 100MA, and looks to be heading for the 200MA:</p>

<p>Here&rsquo;s the chart of $IWM on the daily:</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170927/jd_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170927/jd_daily.png" alt="JD Daily - 2017-09-27" /></a></p>

<p>We&rsquo;re looking for a deeper pullback to the 200MA before getting long this stock, with a stop below the 200MA when it happens.</p>

<p>For now, this is a sit-and-wait situation. We&rsquo;ll keep the stock on our watchlist.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[IWM - New Highs]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/iwm-new-highs/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-27T09:08:10-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/iwm-new-highs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>$IWM has been the leader of the indices. Usually, when something like this happens, people wonder if this is a chart to short. Mean reversion has to happen at some point, and $IWM should correct and come back down, right?</p>

<p>As trend traders, the last thing we want to do to $IWM is to short it. It&rsquo;s fine if we don&rsquo;t get long new highs, but it&rsquo;s definitely not our job to pick the tops and predict price movement. Rather, it&rsquo;s simply our job to follow price - that&rsquo;s it.</p>

<p>Here&rsquo;s the chart of $IWM on the daily:</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170927/iwm_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170927/iwm_daily.png" alt="IWM Daily - 2017-09-27" /></a></p>

<p>Today, we&rsquo;ve put in another new high. The market is clearly signaling that risk is on. For those that are hesitant to get long the $IWM, there are numerous stocks to choose from in the small cap sector. Pick one that&rsquo;s trending up, get in with an appropriate stop placement and position size, and ride the trend for as long as you can.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[VERI - Buy What's Going Up]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/veri-buy-whats-going-up/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-27T08:53:30-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/veri-buy-whats-going-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>$VERI has been a runner over the past few weeks. The question now is, should we short it?</p>

<p>As trend traders, the last thing we want to do to $VERI is to short it. It&rsquo;s nice to paint tops and have our little egos stroked when this thing comes crashing down fast, but trend traders <em>follow</em> the price movement, not predict it.</p>

<p>Here&rsquo;s the chart on the daily:</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170927/veri_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170927/veri_daily.png" alt="VERI Daily - 2017-09-27" /></a></p>

<p>Today, we have a massive red candle engulfing the prior three trading sessions. As far as we&rsquo;re concerned, the overall trend on the daily chart is going up. Ignoring everything else like news, PE ratios, or whatever fundamental analysis, this chart is a screaming long. As Paul Tudor Jones once said:</p>

<blockquote><p>&ldquo;&hellip;at the end of the day, your job is to buy what goes up and to sell what goes down so really who gives a damn about PE’s? If it’s going up you’re supposed to be long it.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>

<p>Put another way, your goal is to jump in on the trend, up or down, depending on your timeframe. How much risk you&rsquo;re willing to put on this trend trade depends on where you place your stop. Conservative trend traders would place a stop below the existing 50MA, and more aggressive trend traders would place it at a closer MA (20MA).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
