<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: trend | Warrior Wealth]]></title>
  <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/categories/trend/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-09-28T22:35:17-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ken Yu]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jumping In On ILMN]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/28/jumping-in-on-ilmn/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-28T22:26:55-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/28/jumping-in-on-ilmn</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While the biotech sector picks up momentum, one can look for opportunities in specific stocks to get long.</p>

<p>One prime example of this is $ILMN. Please observe the chart below.</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170928/ilmn_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170928/ilmn_daily.png" alt="ILMN Daily - 2017-09-28" /></a></p>

<p>$ILMN has come back down to tag the 50MA. One can consider getting long half a piece here, first. Should the stock come down lower to tag the 100MA, the other half can be placed.</p>

<p>Stop loss should be placed just below the 100MA, at around $178.51. This allows for some buffer room below the major moving average to account for potential noise.</p>

<p>More aggressive traders can simply go in with full size, with a stop below the 50MA, around $188.18.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Look at BBRY]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/28/a-look-at-bbry/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-28T22:15:54-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/28/a-look-at-bbry</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>$BBRY has picked up a lot of chatter recently, so let&rsquo;s take a look at the chart of the stock on the daily timeframe.</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170928/bbry_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170928/bbry_daily.png" alt="BBRY Daily - 2017-09-28" /></a></p>

<p>Towards the beginning of the year, $BBRY managed to pierce above the 200MA and trend upwards. In August, prices came back down to tag the 200MA before bouncing higher. While we did not get long this stock at that time, the stock is still a decent candidate to get long right now, with a stop just below the 200MA.</p>

<p>More aggressive traders can place the stop below the 100MA - this allows them to go in with a larger position size, albeit a higher possibility of their getting stopped out should prices come back down.</p>

<p>Should one get long here with a conservative position size, using the 200MA as a reference, the stop would be placed at $8.01.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[BLUE - Breakout to Fresh Highs]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/28/blue-breakout-to-fresh-highs/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-28T07:25:15-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/28/blue-breakout-to-fresh-highs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello traders,</p>

<p>As $BLUE breaks out to new highs, one may consider if it&rsquo;s too late to go long. Let&rsquo;s take a look at the daily chart of $BLUE below.</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170928/blue_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170928/blue_daily.png" alt="BLUE Daily - 2017-09-28" /></a></p>

<p>$BLUE has consistently held the 200MA and 100MA since last year, and we&rsquo;re now seeing the stock trend above the 20MA. This is a signal of a strong upwards trend. While that can change at any moment, current signals point to getting long.</p>

<p>For trend traders, what matters isn&rsquo;t about how much money to make. <strong>Rather, what matters is being in the trend with the right position size, according to your personal risk tolerance, in order to stay in the trend.</strong></p>

<p>Conservative traders would use the 200MA as a reference point when considering where to place their stop as part of the trend trade, while more aggressive traders would use the 20MA, as placing a closer stop allows them to have a bigger position size (albeit getting stopped out earlier should the stock fall down, but maintain trend above the 200MA). Again, this choice is up to the investor, and is one we highly recommend each individual consider before taking on a position in order to be able to hold for the duration of the trend.</p>

<p>Always consider the amount of risk you&rsquo;re willing to take in the position, before you think about potential profits. As long as you manage risk properly, you&rsquo;ll be able to stay with the trend.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: we are currently long $BLUE, with a stop below the 200MA at $85.51 as of the time of writing.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIT - Start of a New Trend]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/fit-start-of-a-new-trend/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-27T15:13:08-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/fit-start-of-a-new-trend</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey traders,</p>

<p>One of the things that we love most are chart patterns that exhibit 200MA breaches. One of the following is of course, $FIT, which has picked up a lot of chatter today.</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170927/fit_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170927/fit_daily.png" alt="FIT Daily - 2017-09-27" /></a></p>

<p>$FIT has breached the 200MA early in September. Breaches like this usually (but not always) signal a reversal and the start of a new trend higher. Without a doubt, $FIT is a long in our books. With proper stop loss placement just below the 200MA at 5.71, we will be looking to ride this stock until it closes below the 200MA. As always, should you get long, size your position according to your personal risk tolerance.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: we are currently long $FIT as of time of writing.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[VCEL - Trending Up]]></title>
    <link href="http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/vcel-trending-up/"/>
    <updated>2017-09-27T15:06:01-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://warriorwealth.github.io/blog/2017/09/27/vcel-trending-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey traders,</p>

<p>One hot stock today is $VCEL. Let&rsquo;s take a look at the chart.</p>

<p><a href="/images/blog/20170927/vcel_daily.png"><img src="/images/blog/20170927/vcel_daily.png" alt="VCEL Daily - 2017-09-27" /></a></p>

<p>$VCEL has breached the 200MA early in July, and held all other moving averages (20, 50, and 100) since then. The momentum continues to the upside, and the trend is strongly upwards. This is, without a doubt, a buy, with a stop loss placed just below the 20MA. While we aren&rsquo;t long this stock, we do have a bullish bias here. As always, should you get long, size your position according to your personal risk tolerance.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
